(Kim Kang Min plays Choi Si Yeol)
(Park Jin Woo plays Na Aijun)
(Byung Hun as Yeon Joo Ha)
(Kim Hongjun plays Ji Kyusung)
("My idol is chasing me?!")
I'm flirting now
From the first time I saw you until now
I've always been...interested
To Teacher Luo Aijun
I don't want you to give me the answer right now
It's still some time before the filming ends
But…
if i contact you
You must answer me
Teacher Luo Aijun
By the way, I want to return the clothes you just borrowed from me.
Let's go
(Episode 4 Do you want to spend tonight with me?)
Ji Kuisheng
(6 months ago)
-Have you eaten? -Have you eaten?
What are you here for?
I just told you to rest at home.
Because I miss you so much
Shi Lie
Yeah
- It's over so soon. - That's right.
Brother Zhuhe said he would come and cheer me up
It seems you have other people you want to meet.
Nope, I'm here to cheer up your performance.
Wait for me before you go for the interview
Wait a moment
It's beautiful here
Don't you think he is suitable for wearing glasses?
Really
So what
You have been dating for so long
do you still like him very much
Yeah, I like it very much
as long as you are happy
so good
That's enough
(Call from Luo Aijun)
Luo Aijun
Yeah
Why are you talking about that? It’s so disgusting.
OK
i love you too
I said I love you too
Is it ok?
Hello Luo Aijun
Don't drink any more before I go.
Okay, I'll be there in a moment
Yeah Brother Zhuhe
Kuisheng said he wanted to break up with me
I don't know what to do
What should I... do?
Luo Aijun
You always forget things
Remember to bring it
What would I do without you?
-I'm leaving. -Yeah
By the way, you know you're in charge of tonight's dinner, right?
Of course I know
Looking forward to the dinner you cooked
You just called me
Are you going to talk about Zhuhe?
You can't treat Brother Zhu He like this
We…
We can't treat Brother Zhu He like that
I want teacher Luo Aijun to guide me
Ji Kyu Sung’s new lover
Me...me? You mean me?
Teacher Luo Aijun
You are my ideal type
Brother Zhuhe
feeling betrayed
I'll help you make him feel the same way
And it’s returned twice as much
let me help you
Chief Chi
Yes
Lianzhu River
You know that he doesn't act in movies, right?
know
I'm really going crazy
What should we do in this situation?
Why did he say he didn't want to act?
if i knew
Are you still waiting here?
In short
First like this
represent
I'd better contact you again and check.
I'm going to find Zhuhe
What are you looking for me for?
Ah that...
Not because...
I haven't seen you for a while
So…
Not because...
I'm worried about you
Films directed by Bai
I heard that you told your representative that you wouldn’t act.
Yeah
The opponent actor is Chen Shuyun
-And for you at this time
The next work is important - now
You are here for...
Did you come here specially to talk about this?
Yeah
I don't act
Please help me convey it to the representative
Even if he and Director Bai come together to convince me
My answer won't change either
Why did you suddenly change your mind?
Not because you want to act
Is that why you have a meeting with the director?
Yes
Because you were next to me at that time
If we want to see each other every day but also avoid being noticed
Then we have to work together more often
There’s no need for that now anyway.
I want to rest
After the filming of this drama ended
So...please help me convey this to the representative
Zhuhe
I still like you very much when I see you now
So I hope you don't appear in front of me
At least be considerate like this
I'm leaving
Golden rice fields in autumn
Dance with the wind
Even if it’s covered in winter snow…
Still green…
Still green
Hey, what's wrong, teacher?
Indicates that this question will be given in the exam
Circle it quickly
Still green
From the first time I saw you until now
I've always been...interested
Incredible dream situation
Although it is like a fog that may dissipate at any time...
Just wait a moment
I want to leave all worries about reality and the future behind
(Choi Si Yeol) Your smell is on my clothes
There is no way to return it to the sponsors
What should I do? I shouldn't have borrowed it from you...
(Choi Si Yeol) This is the best
I will keep this dress well
How can I be so happy? I can’t believe it.
I'm really going crazy
I’m sending one-to-one messages with Choi Si-yeol.
I really can't believe it
And it was he who sent the message to me first.
If he knows I am a fan in the future
What to do
What's going on
-You came back so early today. -Yeah
great
I happen to have something I want to discuss with you
Actually I have a big problem
nothing
You go to sleep
Let me sort it out a little more and then I can discuss it with you.
You go quickly
rest
It shouldn't matter if I put it off for now.
Read and cannot reply
he admitted
I met Kuisheng
He said he did have a new partner
are you okay
I'd say hearing it with your own ears makes it easier to give up.
but i regret it
That sentence becomes more and more profound
The more I think about it, the more uncomfortable I feel
what to do
I feel it will last a long time
I won't do this, brother
I will never let you go
i assure you
thank you
(Teacher Luo Aijun)
Do you want me to remit the dry cleaning fee to you?
can you give me your bank account number
Remittance…
Why don't you treat me to dinner to pay for the dry cleaning?
Do you want to meet today?
do you have an appointment
I…
Sir
Yes, that is…
-The name is... -I have an appointment
Choi Si Yeol
Okay, this way please
Let's go
Shi Yeol’s private server look that has only been seen in videos
I actually saw it with my own eyes
Although I shouldn’t say such things to the holy Si Yeol
But just once
I really want to touch the back of his neck
what do you want to eat
The back of the neck...what are you talking about?
I…
(Top-quality pork neck steak with rich flavor 99,000 won)
I want to eat pork neck...
Sorry
please give us this and this
This needs to be bottled
OK
Restaurants and cuisine are all decided by me.
Let me treat you today
Teacher Luo
You'll treat me next time
No. How can I...
This way we can meet again next time
Is the food to your liking?
Yeah, it suits my taste very well.
I eat school meals every day
It’s only thanks to you that I can come to such a wonderful place.
I'll treat you to better food next time
Come and sit at my house
what
I'm pretty good at cooking.
Are you good at cooking?
You must be very busy. How come you still have time to learn how to cook?
You are omnipotent... No
I mean...
When is the next shooting?
If you want to promote the album and shoot a variety show at the same time
You should be very tired
very interesting
Because I can use shooting as an excuse
Keep meeting the people you want to meet
What's going on? Is he talking about me?
Is this really teasing me?
Isn’t it my fantasy?
So have you considered what I said?
i'm very interested in you
If you are already in a relationship…
Dating partner…
No
OK
No need to pick up the red wine glass
Just take it like this
good
"My idol is chasing me?!"
You can't even tell if it's a dream or reality
How dare you kiss Shi Yeol?
what
Hickey?
I have become less popular as I get older, and I still like to pretend to be a big name.
Hey, he will hear you
Not to mention spare clothes
You don’t even have a set of clothes today?
I have my reasons
How about taking this opportunity to wear couple clothes?
Are you interested in me now too?